No Rule Partnership has just started and
it's been almost a year.
We collaborated with various companies
and organizations throughout Japan.
This project started with the feeling of
gratitude for the 15th anniversary.
We felt that we were being asked to be
idols to make Japan happy.
So, in 2024, we will evolve this No Rule
Partnership into the next step.
Not only us, but also the female idol
section of Stardust Promotion,
and the members of Stardust Planet.
We are the members of Stardust
Promotion, the company with 69
employees.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Mugen company, STAPRA.
As the name suggests,
we aim to create an infinite possibility
with a non-rule collaboration with 69
idols from all over Japan and STARDUST
PLANET.
69 STAPRA members will use their
individuality and entertainment power as
employees.
We will solve the problems of companies,
organizations and stores and cheer up
the Japanese people.
So, Mugen Company STAPRA will start
today.
Today, April 1st, many companies are
holding the inauguration ceremony
nationwide.
In a sense, Mugen Company STAPRA also
celebrated the inauguration ceremony
today.
Speaking of the company, who is the
president?
Who is the president?
President...
But the oldest is...
Emi-chan?
It was a surprise.
Because she is the oldest.
If you say the age, I will be the
oldest.
But...
At the end of the day, I'm the best
I think so too
I think I can do it well too
Everyone can do it
But I'm the same age as A-rin
So your age doesn't matter
But I really respect A-rin
I think I'll go from Nagoya
But I want to do it too
There are many people who want to do it
Right?
I want to be the president
I really admire the president
President is the best
Can you raise your hand a little bit
earlier?
Sorry
Everyone raised their hands
Then I will
No, no, no
What's different?
Please forgive me
Leader, not president
Then who will ask for it?
What?
I'm the only one
I'm going back
Then, well,
It's a very good company with a good
wind
I see
Let's be friends
Let's do our best together
Yes
Thank you